const grade4data=[
    {
        question:"drama",
        choices:["劇","ドラム","脚本家","感動的な"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"hear",
        choices:["髪","ここ","聞く","耳"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"quick",
        choices:["素早い","静かな","クイズ","クリックする"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"rich",
        choices:["ライチ","お金","高級品","裕福な"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"subway",
        choices:["高速道路","幹線道路","鉄道","地下鉄"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"get off",
        choices:["手放す","降りる","伏せる","漏れる"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"put away",
        choices:["奪う","無視する","放置する","片付ける"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"take off",
        choices:["持ち帰る","脱ぐ","切り取る","解放する"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"turn on",
        choices:["曲がる","(電気を)つける","回転する","(利益を)得る"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"by the way",
        choices:["その方法で","従って","ところで","一方で"],
        answer:2
    }
]

export default grade4data;